buxptr.com 2010-12-12

# BuxPtr.com - earn from home&have fun&BuxPtr.com

Members: **29,939** | Active members: **29,939** | Total debits: **1.213.656.00$**

**Privacy Policy**

 **Date of last modification:** 11 May 2008

This privacy policy sets out how BuxPtr.com uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website. BuxPtr.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. BuxPtr.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

 **#What we collect** We may collect the following information: name / contact information including email address / payment account information.

 **#What we do with the information we gather** We require this information to provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: Internal record keeping; We may periodically send information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

 **#Security** We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect online.

 **#How we use cookies** A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

 **#Links to other websites** Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **#Controlling your personal information** We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
